#### Contact

edita.motuze@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/editamotuzė-122595209 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

React Query Redux.js Git

# Edita Motuzė

### Front-end developer

Kaunas, Kauno, Lithuania

## Summary

I am public health specialist and even though I am doing great in this field, in the last few years I have had the feeling that I am not in the field where I would like to spend my whole life. So I decided that I wanted to retrain and started learning HTML, CSS and JavaScript on my own. After few month of self-learning I started and completed frontend courses at Code Academy (React.js, Node.js, basics of Typescript, Git and etc.), internship at Cognizant and various online courses to gain knowledge about React Query, Redux and other libriries.

My latest work: https://mountain-cabin.netlify.app , https://github.com/editaMot/mountain-cabin

## Experience

Kauno miesto savivaldybės visuomenės sveikatos biuras 5 years 3 months

Public procurement specialist October 2021 - October 2023 (2 years 1 month)

Public Health Specialist August 2018 - October 2023 (5 years 3 months)

### Cognizant

Frontend Developer (internship) October 2022 - January 2023 (4 months)

Kaunas, Kauno, Lithuania

Project "Sourcery Academy website" implementation with the team.

#### Covered topics:

- Agile & Git
- JS Fundamentals
- React Fundamentals & advanced
- Project Structure & Dynamic Components

Page 1 of 2

- HTML Semantics & BEM
- CSS Basics
- Accessibility & SCSS Basics
- SCSS in depth
- Accessibility in depth
- Build tools
- Testing

Kauno lopšelis darželis Liepaitė Dietitian August 2017 - December 2019 (2 years 5 months)

# Education

CodeAcademy

Frontend · (October 2021 - September 2022)

Lithuanian University of Health Sciences

Master's degree, Public Health Management · (2018 - 2020)

Lithuanian University of Health Sciences
Bachelor's degree, Public Health (2014 - 2018)